How could someone crush sales in 2022?
My biggest advice to most salesmen
is no one likes to be
sold to, but everybody likes to buy.
So what you do is you
put something in front of them
and I call it solution selling.
There's lots of names for it.
I sell by asking questions,
understanding first what the real true need is,
and then see if I
can help them solve that need.
I don't come in and say,
a lot of young salespeople come in and say,
hey, let me do a demo.
Let me show you everything I got.
And when you see something, stop me.
And that's just the wrong way to sell.
That's like throwing shit against the wall
and seeing what sticks.
What I'm saying is slow down,
do a lot of homework on your client
before you ever show up,
because nobody does that,
understand their pain points,
and make sure you're talking to them
about those pain points and mutually solve a problem
as opposed to trying to sell them
something like off the back of a truck.